Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- Saaty, 1977-1994 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Sachs, Jonathan, [1993?] (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Sachs, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- Sakashita, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Sandler, after 1991? (Box 115, Folder 12)
- Saperstein, 1992-1993 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Schuler, 1992-1994 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- Sieglie, 1988-1996 (Box 115, Folder 15)
- Seitz, Steve, 1985-1993 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- Sen, Amartya, 1991-1997 (Box 115, Folder 17)
- Sen, Somnath, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 18)
- Singer, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 19)
- Ron Smith, 1997 (Box 115, Folder 20)
- Solomon, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 21)
- Stern, Haveman, Deardorff, 1981-1992 (Box 115, Folder 22)
- Suarez, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 23)
- Suits, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 24)
- Smith, Ron, 1977-1990 (Box 115, Folder 25)
- Szyrmer, after 1988? (Box 115, Folder 26)
- Tao-Ran, 1995-1996 (Box 115, Folder 27)
- Tallant, 1991-1993 (Box 115, Folder 28)
- Temenggung, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 29)
- Thrall, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 30)
- Thorbecke, 1989-1991 (Box 115, Folder 31A)
- Thorbecke, 1988-1989 (Box 115, Folder 31B)
- Tinbergen, [N.D.] (Box 115, Folder 32)
- Treddenick, 1994 (Box 115, Folder 33)
- Tsukidate, 1995-1996 (Box 115, Folder 34)
- Udis, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 35)
- Stewart, 1948-1959 (Box 115, Folder 36)
- Vickrey, Bill, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 37)
- Warf, after 1991? (Box 115, Folder 38)
- Weida, 1990-1996 (Box 115, Folder 39)
- Weidenbaum, 1988-1992 (Box 115, Folder 40)
- Weiss, Dorothy, 1995 (Box 115, Folder 41)
- Weiss, 1983-1993 (Box 115, Folder 42)
- Weisman, Jason, 1994-1997 (Box 115, Folder 43)
- Willumsen, 1990-1991 (Box 115, Folder 44)
- Wolfson, 1989-1992 (Box 115, Folder 45)
- Xie, Jian, 1992-1995 (Box 115, Folder 46)
- Yaman, 1994? (Box 115, Folder 47)
- Yoon, 1992 (Box 115, Folder 48)
- Young, Peyton, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 49)
- Cheng-I Yu, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 50)
- Yunker, after 1991? (Box 115, Folder 51)
- Zinnes, after 1992? (Box 115, Folder 52)
- Isard-Miscellaneous Items, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 53)
  Isard notes
- Miscellaneous Notes for Isard's Arms Race Book, [N.D.] (Box 115, Folder 54)
- Blaine Lewis, after 1897? (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Lee, Ju-Ho, after 1981? (Box 116, Folder 2)
- Lo, Fu-chen, 1990-1994 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- M, 1964-1999 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Matchek, Dale C., 1987-2008 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- McGraw Hill, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Macmillan, 1987-1997 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- NIRA, 1991-1992 (Box 116, Folder 8)
- N, 1987-1996 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- McGraw Hill, 1990 (Box 116, Folder 10)
- MIT Press, 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 11)
- Ninshina, Katsumi PhD/RS, 1978-1984 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- North Holland, 1979-1998 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- North Holland, Peace Economics and Peace Science Journal, 1990-1999 (Box 116, Folder 14)
- North Holland-Book, 1989-1998 (Box 116, Folder 15)
- Norton, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 16)
- NYU Press, 1990-1991 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- O, 1987-1997 (Box 116, Folder 18)
- Okita, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 19)
- Oxford U Press, 1986-1995 (Box 116, Folder 20)
- P, 1985-1999 (Box 116, Folder 21)
- Pion, 1998 (Box 116, Folder 22)
- Princeton U Press, 1996 (Box 116, Folder 23)
- R, 1985-1995 (Box 116, Folder 24)
- Rima, 1991-1996 (Box 116, Folder 25)
- Romanos, Mike, 1990-1993 (Box 116, Folder 26)
- Russett and JCR (Journal of Conflict Resolution), 1985-1990 (Box 116, Folder 27)
- S, 1985-1998 (Box 116, Folder 28)
- T, S, 1995-1998 (Box 116, Folder 29)
- Sakashita, 1988-1992 (Box 116, Folder 30)
- Saltzman, 1987-1996 (Box 116, Folder 31)
- Sasaki, 1987-1997 (Box 116, Folder 32)
- Smith, Christine, 1984-1991 (Box 116, Folder 33)
- Early Notes on Unity and Old Ideas, 1974-1994 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  Notes and Drafts for Isard's Unity book
- Preface, 1984-1994 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- New Chapters # I, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Chap 2, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Chap 3 Teilhard, 1992-1993 (Box 117, Folder 5)
- Chap 4 Dauhius et. al, 1991-1993 (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Notes for Isard's Unity Book, 1984-1993 (Box 117, Folder 7)
- Chap 5, 1988-1994 (Box 117, Folder 8)
- Chap 6 Cellular Automata and Bohm, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 9)
- Chap 7 GUTs etc, 1970-1994 (Box 117, Folder 10)
- Chap 8, 1992-1993 (Box 117, Folder 11)
- Chap 9, 1991-1993 (Box 117, Folder 12)
- Chap 9A, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 13)
- Chap 10 draft, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 14A)
- Chap 10, 1975-1993 (Box 117, Folder 14B)
- Chap 11 Draft, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 15A)
- Chap 11 Draft 2, [after 1993?] (Box 117, Folder 15B)
- Chap 11, 1983-1994 (Box 117, Folder 15C)
- Chap 12, after 1994? (Box 117, Folder 16)
- Chap 13/new Chap 11, 1992-1994 (Box 117, Folder 17A)
- New Chap 11, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 17B)
- Chap 11 Draft (1995 version), 1995 (Box 117, Folder 18)
- Chap 12 Music, 1975 (Box 117, Folder 19)
- Strings, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 20)
- Abraham, 1993 (Box 117, Folder 21)
- Adair, 1995 (Box 117, Folder 22)
  Notes, scanned copy of article
- Bronowski, after 1970? (Box 117, Folder 23)
- Augus, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 24)
- Barlow, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 25)
- Brush, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 26)
- Cesani (Csanyi) and Kampis, after 1989? (Box 117, Folder 27)
- Dauhius, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 28)
- Doolittle, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 29)
- Entropy, Statistical Mechanics, Equal. Thermodyanamics DEF etc., [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 30)
  Article, notes
- Gleich, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 31)
- Grene, 1988-1993 (Box 117, Folder 32)
- Hopfield, 1982-1984 (Box 117, Folder 33)
- Klir, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 34)
- Koestler, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 35)
- Koschmieder, after 1991? (Box 117, Folder 36)
  Scans of book
- Kosko, 1992 (Box 117, Folder 37)
- Laszlo, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 38)
- Layzer, 1974-1992 (Box 117, Folder 39)
  Articles, notes
- Lewontin, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 40)
- Lovelock, [N.D.] (Box 117, Folder 41)
- Moon, after 1986? (Box 117, Folder 42)
- Pagel, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 43)
- Pattee, 1975-1991 (Box 117, Folder 44A)
- Pattee 2, 1988 (Box 117, Folder 44B)
- Pattee 3, 1977-1992 (Box 117, Folder 44C)
- Lecture-Unification of China, July 24, 1992 Taiwan, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- On Future Direction of Reg'l Science XXXth French Anniversary-1992, 1987-1992 (Box 118, Folder 2)
- Rotterdam 4th World Peace Science Con. May 1992, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 3)
- Hague EW Conference May 1992, 1992 (Box 118, Folder 4)
- PSSI-AEA Paper New Orleans Jan 3, 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 5)
- Regional Conflicts-ARSW-Japan Conf. Dec 1991, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 6)
- New Directions in CMP's PSSI Ann Arbor Nov 91, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 7)
- World Modelling on Consequences of Military Expenditures-July 1991 Chatterji, 1991-1992 (Box 118, Folder 8)
- Stockholm June 1991 Peace Lecture, 1991 (Box 118, Folder 9)
- Notre Dame Conference 11/30-12/1/90, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 10)
- Progress in Global Modelling Dec 1989, 1989? (Box 118, Folder 11A)
- Progress in Global Modelling Draft, 1989? (Box 118, Folder 11B)
- Key Directions-PSSI Rutgers Nov 1990, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 12)
- AEA-ECAAR Paper Dec 1990 Wash D.C., 1990? (Box 118, Folder 13)
- Notre Dame Paper-Use of Outlines only Dec 1,1990, 1991? (Box 118, Folder 14)
- Summary Paper PRSCO Summer Institute Bandung, Indonesia July 1990, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 15)
- Visionary Notes-Karlsrule-Feb 1990 Funck's 60th, 1990 (Box 118, Folder 16)
- CMPS Paper: Progress in Global Modelling Vol 11 #1, [N.D.] (Box 118, Folder 17)
- PSSI Paper Nov 1989 Ohio State University, 1989? (Box 118, Folder 18)
- ASSA PSSI Paper Dec 28, 1989 Atlanta, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 19)
- On Bilateral Trade Matrix Projection 8/30/89, [N.D.] (Box 118, Folder 20A)
- Bilateral Trade Matrix Projection Draft, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 20B)
- Bilateral Trade Matrix Projection Notes, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 20C)
- On Operationalizing the Trade Variable in a Funck-type Multi-Region Global Model 9/1/89, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 21)
- Economic-Ecologic Conflicts Binghamton May 1989, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 22)
- July 10, 1988 1000 and one PhD Topics, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 23A)
- A Thousand and One PhD Topics Draft, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 23B)
- March 10, 1988 Preliminary Statement on Demographics to attendees at Dissertation Questioning Umea, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 24)
- PSSI Paper Cambridge Nov 1987 Global Economic Modelling PSIG, 1987? (Box 118, Folder 25)
- COPRED Talk-Milwaukee-Peace Studies at the Crossroads Nov 1987, 1964-1987 (Box 118, Folder 26)
- ECAAR 1989-1990, 1989-1990 (Box 118, Folder 27)
- ECAAR 1991, 1990-1992 (Box 118, Folder 28)
- Brandford, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Bray, 1990-1995 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- C, 1985-1998 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Cambridge U. Press, 1986-2006 (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Chatterji, 1988-1996 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- U of Chicago Press, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- China Nat'l Research Center, 1991-1994 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- China Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- China Conference, Yang, Oct 11-14, 1993, 1992-1996 (Box 119, Folder 9)
- China-Yang-RSA Conference, 1993-1995 (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Chen Zongxing, 1992-1993 (Box 119, Folder 11)
- Chen Chiu, Lee-in, 1990-1993 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- Jicheng China, 1987-1993 (Box 119, Folder 13)
- Chinese Scholars, 1991-1996 (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Cornell U Press, 1995 (Box 119, Folder 15)
- Dunn, Ed, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- Domanski, 1985-1992 (Box 119, Folder 17)
- Duncan, Keith, 1992-1993 (Box 119, Folder 18)
- DDIR, 1986-1987 (Box 119, Folder 19)
- Dean, Bill, 1988-1990 (Box 119, Folder 20)
- Dacey and Idaho, 1988-1993 (Box 119, Folder 21)
- D, 1985-1998 (Box 119, Folder 22)
- E, 1987-1999 (Box 119, Folder 23)
- F, 1985-1998 (Box 119, Folder 24)
- Fogarty, 1986-1989 (Box 119, Folder 25)
- Fontanel, 1992-1994 (Box 119, Folder 26)
- Free Press, 1989-1995 (Box 119, Folder 27)
- G, 1977-2001 (Box 119, Folder 28)
- Goldberg, Gary, 1971-1989 (Box 119, Folder 29)
- H, 1985-1998 (Box 119, Folder 30)
- Haffar, 1995-1999 (Box 119, Folder 31)
- Hattori Japan visit, 1990-1997 (Box 119, Folder 32)
- Hewings, 1993-1997 (Box 119, Folder 33)
- I, 1985-2000 (Box 119, Folder 34)
- Isard-official Cornell and Binghamton and Penn, 1985-2004 (Box 119, Folder 35)
- J, 1986-1998 (Box 119, Folder 36)
- JCER, 1990-1991 (Box 119, Folder 37)
- JAI, 1955 (Box 119, Folder 38)
- Japan Foundation-GCP, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 39)
- Johns Hopkins Press, 1990-1991 (Box 119, Folder 40)
- K, 1985-1998 (Box 119, Folder 41)
- Kawashima, 1996-1997 (Box 119, Folder 42)
- L, 1981-1999 (Box 119, Folder 43)
- Katsumata, Rikuo, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 1)
- Kawashima, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Kim, E, 1988-1993 (Box 120, Folder 3)
- Klein and LINK, 1977-1996 (Box 120, Folder 4)
- Kowert, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 5)
- Krugman, Paul, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 6)
- Kuenne, 1988-1992 (Box 120, Folder 7)
- Kugler, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 8)
- Kutet, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 9)
- Langlois, 1990-1995 (Box 120, Folder 10)
- Launhardt, 1988-1991 (Box 120, Folder 11)
- Lee, Bong Gyou, 1992-1994 (Box 120, Folder 12)
- Lee, Hung Seok (Hyung-Seog), 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 13)
- Leng, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 14)
- Leontief et al, 1951-1987 (Box 120, Folder 15)
- Li, Hyung-Yu (Hung Yi), after 1989? (Box 120, Folder 16)
- Liew, 1985 (Box 120, Folder 17)
- Lim, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 18)
- Lindbeck, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 19)
- Lindgren, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 20)
- Lobo, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 21)
- Looney, 1986-1989 (Box 120, Folder 22)
- Lotov, 1987-1992 (Box 120, Folder 23)
- Lundborg, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 24)
- Lyons, 1991 (Box 120, Folder 25)
- Manning, Diana, 1989-1992 (Box 120, Folder 26)
- Markusen, 1992-1997 (Box 120, Folder 27)
- Marlin, after 1996? (Box 120, Folder 28)
- McClelland, Peter, after 1995? (Box 120, Folder 29)
- McGuire, 1987-1995 (Box 120, Folder 30)
- McGinnis, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 31)
- McNamara, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 32)
- Meagher, 1982 (Box 120, Folder 33)
- Merritt, after 1965? (Box 120, Folder 34)
- Menshikov, 1994-1995 (Box 120, Folder 35)
- Min, Dong Li, 1996 (Box 120, Folder 36)
- Mintz, 1989-1991 (Box 120, Folder 37)
- Nabe, 1983 (Box 120, Folder 38)
- Nagurney, 1990 (Box 120, Folder 39)
- Nishiura, 1989 (Box 120, Folder 40)
- Okamura, after 1988? (Box 120, Folder 41)
- O'Loughlin, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 42)
- Olson, Mancur, mid-1960's? (Box 120, Folder 43)
- Paelinck, 1996 (Box 120, Folder 44)
- Parr-1998 Export Stages, 1998? (Box 120, Folder 45)
- Pasetta, Vesna, 1992-1993 (Box 120, Folder 46)
- Patchen, after 1991? (Box 120, Folder 47)
- Petersen, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 48)
- Polachek, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 49)
- Pollins, 1986 (Box 120, Folder 50)
- Radner, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 51)
- Outgoing correspondence, August 1981 - December 1981 (Box 121, Folder 1)
- Outgoing correspondence, January 1982 - March 1982 (Box 121, Folder 2)
- Outgoing correspondence, March 1982 - June 1982 (Box 121, Folder 3)
- Outgoing correspondence, July 1982 - August 1982 (Box 121, Folder 4)
- Outgoing correspondence, May 1983 (Box 121, Folder 5)
- Outgoing correspondence, June 1983 - September 1983 (Box 121, Folder 6)
- Outgoing correspondence, October 1983 - December 1983 (Box 121, Folder 7)
- Outgoing correspondence, January 1984 - April 1984 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Photos of Isard, n.d.; CD-1946